# KOTIBAH MOHAMAD

### FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER





+963991100863



kotibahmohamad@gmail.com



syria/Damascus



https://kotibah99.github.io/personal-website/

### PROFILE

I have 3 years of experiences in development, +2 years in team leading and 1 year in system analysis, installation, testing and maintenance of software systems. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team I am currently creating my own page kotibah\_4\_IT in order to provide technical information to everyone, her name is kotibah\_4\_IT on Instgram and facebook

## SKILLS

- Web Design
- Design Thinking.responsive Design
- Html,css,bootstrap,sql,git,jQuery
- Front End Coding
- Problem-Solving
- javascript,react.js,node.js,redux
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication,socialMedia
  Expert

## EXPERIENCE

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

shamra company

2018-2020

- Database administration and website design
- finshed 3web application with responsive mobile

#### **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

pro gym moualla

2021-2022

 I designed the idea and turned it into a code and linked the branches together

## **EDUCATION**

#### MASTER OF WEB SCIENCE

syrian virtual university 01/2023-present

## BACHELOR OF SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Tishreen University

09/2017 -

09/2022

#### CEO

alHarm for money transfers 2022-2023

 Responsible for external transfers, cashiers, reception, monitoring cameras and their connections

## KOTIBAH MOHAMAD





## LANGEUAGES

## **PROJECT**

**ARABIC** 

native or Bilingual proficiency

**ENGISH** 

full professional proficiency

**ON GITHUB** 

https://github.com/kotibah99

## INTERESTS

CHESS, KARATE, BODYBULDING, READING

## ACHIEVEMENTS

I OWN A PAGE KOTIBAH\_4\_IT TO SOLVE PEOPLE'S DAILY PROBLEMS WITH MATTERS RELATED TO SOCIAL MEDIA AND OTHERS, AND TO DISTRIBUTE PRIZES